Guide to the Labor Union Constitutions, By-Laws and Agreements collection, 1883-1999 LAC0012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Constitutions and By-Laws, 1883-1986; Series 1; 9 Linear Feet
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1935-1964; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Retired Civil Employees, 1952; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - National Executive Board of the American Wire Weavers, 1939; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Rural Letter Carriers' Association, 1946-1955; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - National Union United Welders of America, 1950; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Organization Masters, mates and Pilots, 1936-1949; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - National Maritime Union of America, 1937-1951; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NC and STL Ry Clerks Association, 1937; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association of the United States and Canada, May 1953; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1931-1937; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Order of the Railway Conductors Roster and By Laws of Rochester Division, number Eight, 1924; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Order of Railway Conductors Constitution, 1934-1962; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Order of Railway Conductors Constitution, 1934-1962; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Order of Railroad Telegrapher, 1930-1960; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Oil Workers International Union, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ohio State Legislative Board Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1939; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Office Employees International Union, 1947-1955; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Coast Marine Firemen, Gilers, Watertenders and Wipers Association, 1952; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, January, 1951; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Parters Industrial Organization of the C and NW, 1926; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Pattern Makers League of North America, 1950; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Paving Cutters' Union, 1948; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania System Fraternity, 1922-1931; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Playthings, Jewelry, and Novelty Workers, 1946-1948; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Progressive Mine Workers of America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Protective Order of Dining Car Waiters Local 465, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Protective Order of Railroad Trainmen, 1920; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pullman Car Employees of the Repair Shops, 1937; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Pullman Car Employes Association of the Repair Shop, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Employes National Pension Association, 1932-1944; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Railroad Yardmasters of North America inc., 1925-1954; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Railway Express Chauffers and Helpers, 1939; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Railway Express Employees Local no. 459, 1936; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Railway Labor Executives Assocation, 1961; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1921-1958; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Railway mail Association, 1945-1947; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Railway Patrolmen's International Union, 1954; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Industrial Union, 1952; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Retail Clerks International Association A.F. of L., 1939-1951; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union C.I.O., 1946; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Federation of Civil Service Employees, 1955; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Roofers' Protective Union local no. 28, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Seafarers International Union Proposed Consititution, 1948; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Seafarers International Union of North America, 1931-1963; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1935-1958; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Assocation, 1935-1958; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Shop Crafts Association southern Pacific Lines, 1927-1931; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Shop Employes Association Union Pacific System, 1922-1924; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Shop Employes Association Wabash Railway, 1926-1928; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Soo Line Shop Employes Association, 1930; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1940-1954; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Steel Workers Federation, 1949; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Stove Mounters International Union, 1944-1950; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America [Part 1 of 2], 1933-1963; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America [Part 2 of 2], 1933-1963; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Textile Workers Union of America CIO, 1939-1956; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Tobacco Workers International Union, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Transport Workers Union of America, 1946-1955; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Transport Workers Union of Greater New York, Local 100, 1950; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, 1946-1951; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - United Association of Office Sales and Technical Employees, 1951; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1929; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1905; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, 1946; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1954; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union Constitution, May 1950; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - United Mine Workers of America District 50, 1947; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1944; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - United National Association of Post Office Clerks, 1941-1950; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America CIO, 1947-1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - United Paperworkers of America, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1951; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - United Public Workers of America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1964; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - United Slate, Tile, and Composition Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers Association, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - United Steel Workers of America, 1942-1952; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1951-1965; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - United Stone and Aliies Products Workers of America, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - United Textile Workers of America, 1944-1950; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - United Transport Service Employees, 1942-1952; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - United Wall Paper Craftsmen and Workers of North America, 1951-1952; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - United Railroad Operating Crafts, 1952-1954; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - United Transportation Union, 1972; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Upholsters' International Union of North America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1946-1954; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Utility Workers Union of America, 1946-1951; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Washburn Memorial Hospital Association, May 1, 1971; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Window Glass Cutters League of America, 1947-1951; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Woman's International Bowling Congress, 1949-1950; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers' International Union, 1946-1976; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Writers Guild of America, West Inc., 1955; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Wire Workers Federal Labor Union, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Yardmasters and Station masters Association, Inc., 1930; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Constitution, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Sixteenth Convention Records and Agreements, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - CIO District 9 Bowling League, 1947; Series 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stages Employes and Moving Picture and Projecting Machine Operators Constitution and By-Laws, 1923, 1935; LAC 0012 Series 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1910-1999; Series 2; 7 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged alphabetically by union.
  This series contains contract and working condition agreements between unions and their employers, dating from 1910-2009. The majority of represented unions are related to the railroad industry, including the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees. Also included are agreements made by the United Steelworkers of America, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, and a variety of other labor organizations. Further, the series contains the 1970 National Master Freight Agreement, the 1936 Washington Agreement, and a Miscellaneous file comprised of correspondence, newspaper clippings, reports and other material.
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric and Motor Coach Employees of Americ, 1937 January 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    General
    Agreement with the Oakland Terminal Railroad Co.
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1954 February 8; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Agreement with the First National Stores, Inc.
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Agreement with Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority, May 1995 - April 1998; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Government Employees National Agreement with the General Services Administration, September 1990; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Government Employees National Agreement with the Social Security Administration, March 1996; Series 2 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Express Workers, 1925 August 7; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Agreement with the American Railway Express Company.
  - American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1949 September 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company.
  - American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1975 April 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Agreement with the Union Pacific Railroad Company.
  - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1954 June 10; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the railroads represented by the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees.
  - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1966 June 16; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Agreement with the carriers represented by the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees of the National Railway labor Conference.
  - Arthur Morgan Trucking Co, Daniel Hamm Drayage Co., 1955; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Associated General Contractors of America Inc., n.d.; Series 2; Undated agreement between the Associated General Contractors of American Inc. with the International Brotherhood of the Teamsters; for further Master Agreements with the Teamsters and other unions based in California, see LAC0012 Box 31, "Papers" 1953-1996. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - General Contractors of America Inc.-Southern California Master Labor Agreements, 1956-1958; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General Contractors of America Inc.-Northern and Central California Master Labor Agreements, 1956-1958; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 1955-1961; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 1962-1964; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 1965-1969; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 15 May 1970; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 1 May 1974-1977; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Associated General Contractors of Missouri, 1980-1986; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Associated General Contractors of St. Louis [1], 1955-1969; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Associated General Contractors of St. Louis [2], 1969-1980; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Associated Yardmasters of the Deleware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company, 1937 August 15; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the Deleware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company.
  - Associated Laundry Owners of Greater St. Louis, the St. Louis Dry Cleaners Exchange, 1969-1972; Series 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Association of Consolidated Metal Crafts, Helpers and Apprentices, AT and SF Railway System, 1937 July 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Agreement with the Atchison, Topkea and Santa Fe Railway System.
  - Association of Machinists, Helpers and Apprentices, AT and SF Railway System, et. al., 1929 January 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    "Agreement covering wages and working conditions of machinists, boilermakers, blacksmiths, sheet-metal workers, electrical workers, carmen, their helpers and apprentices. Also coach cleaners."
  - Association of Maintenance of Way Formen, Mechanics and Helpers of the Burlington Railroad, 1927 November 21; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company.
  - Association of Mechanical Department Employes of Fort Worth Denver City Railway and Wichita Valley Railway, 1929 March 16; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Agreement with the Fort Worth and Denver City Railway Company and the Wichita Valley Railway Company.
  - Association of Mechanical Department Employes of Fort Worth Denver City Railway and Wichita Valley Railway, 1936 February 12; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Association of Oregon Corrections Employees, 1999 July 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Agreement with the State of Oregon.
  - Association of Shop Craft Employees of the Southern Pacific Lines, 1929 March 16; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the Southern Pacific Lines.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et. al., 1937 August 26; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Agreement with the National Carriers' Conference Committee.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et. al., 1937 October 3; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Agreement of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginement, Order of Railyway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Switchmen's Union of North America with the Carriers' Conference Committee.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1941 December 1; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Agreement with the Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1946 May 26; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Agreement with the Eastern, Western and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1946 June 26; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Agreement with the Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et. al., 1948 November 12; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, et. al., 1950 December 21; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1954 August 17; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1972 April 15; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, et. al., 1941 December; Series 2 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1942 July 2; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Agreement with the Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad.
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, et. al., 1944 May 17; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, et. al., 1946 April 19; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, et. al., 1946 May 25; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1954 January 9; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1958 October 16; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Agreement with the Union Pacific Railroad.
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1919 December 16; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Agreement with the United States Railroad Administration.
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1942 August 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1949 September 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1955 September 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Kansas City Southern Railway Co., Arkansas Western Railway Co., Forth Smith and Van Buren Railway Co., and Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co.
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1958 May 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, et. al., 1971 February 10; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Agreement of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and the Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union with the National Railway Labor Conference.
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1973 April 1-27; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1920 February 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1943 June 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Agreement with the Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Long Island Rail Road Co., and Baltimore and Eastern Railroad Railroad Co.
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1945 February 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1945 May 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1946 April 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Agreement with the Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1962 April 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1942 July 2; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1944 November 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad.
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1949 July 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Agreement with the Southern Railway Company
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1958 October 16; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1958 November 1; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Agreement with the Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1920 January 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1923 April 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Agreement with the New York Central Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1938 Feburary 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Agreement with the Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1938 March 17; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Agreement with the Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1938 March 25; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Agreement with the Belt Railway Company of Chicago.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Experess and Station Employees, 1938 September 15; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Agreement with the Texas Mexican Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1938 October 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Agreement with the Southern Railway Company, the Cincinnati, New Orleans and Texas Pacific Railway Company, et. al.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1941 January 16; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Agreement with the Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1941 December 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Agreement with the Railway Express Agency, Inc.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1943 January 11; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Agreement with the Indianapolis Union Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1944 November 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Agreement with the Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railway.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1945 April 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Agreement with the Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1945 August 2; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Agreement with the Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1946 January 16; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1946 February 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Agreement with the Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1952 February 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1956 January 16; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1956 November 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Agreement with the National Carloading Corporation.
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1957 December 18; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1967 January 1; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Experess and Station Employees, 1967 July 15; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Experess and Station Employees, 1967 November 7; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Agreement with the Greath Northern Pacific and Burlingon Lines, Inc.